[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Charleton Heston movie won Best Picture at the 32nd annual Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Ben Hur", "incorrect_answers": ["The 10 Commandments", "Earthquake", "Planet of the Apes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the number of fundamental interactions.", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "8", "6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ceilidh, pronounced /KAY lee/, is a traditional wedding dance in this country.", "correct_answer": "Scotland", "incorrect_answers": ["Argentina", "Spain", "Hungary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of jam is used for the preparation of the traditional South African dessert Malva Pudding?", "correct_answer": "Apricot jam", "incorrect_answers": ["Strawberry jam", "Blueberry jam", "Raspberry jam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 13-tile variation of Mahjong, which of the following is a possible winning hand?", "correct_answer": "4 pongs and a pair of identical tiles", "incorrect_answers": ["2 kongs and a pair of identical tiles", "3 pongs and a chow", "4 kongs and a chow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Facing the Giants, what player transferred to Shiloh after being kicked out of Westview High School?", "correct_answer": "Matt Prater", "incorrect_answers": ["Brock Kelley", "Brady Owens", "David Childers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The island of Sebatik, located east of Borneo, is shared by Indonesia and what other nation?", "correct_answer": "Malaysia", "incorrect_answers": ["The Philippines", "Singapore", "Brunei"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The pores of Kohn are organs located in this part of the human body.", "correct_answer": "Lungs", "incorrect_answers": ["Skin", "Tongue", "Intestines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who did Alan Rickman portray in Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves?", "correct_answer": "the Sheriff of Nottingham", "incorrect_answers": ["Friar Tuck", "Big John", "Robin Hood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does WFM mean when used in instant messaging?", "correct_answer": "works for me", "incorrect_answers": ["works for money", "white female methodist", "with fond memories"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color are wild goldfish?", "correct_answer": "Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Silver", "Orange", "Yellow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The human facial skull consists of double as well as single bones. Which of the following bones is not a facial bone?", "correct_answer": "Calcaneus", "incorrect_answers": ["Zygomatic bone", "Vomer bone", "Mandible"]}]